and then I'll freak you out and you'll
run away.
[music]
Good morning. Happy happy Sunday. I know
usually I feel like I kind of start the
vlogs off with like me like screaming in
your face, but also like sometimes we do
just need to slow it down. And [music] I
know that me saying that kind of doesn't
make as much sense since I'm the reason
why I would always be sped up on the
channel, but the beginning of this is
just going to be calm. Okay, I want you
to take a second. I want you to breathe
with me. Get get a perfume real quick.
It'll be nice. Preferably if you have
something like lavender or eucalyptus.
I missed my hand. Here we go.
Just breathe it in. You know, smells a
little bit like alcohol, but that's
okay.
I don't really know what else to say.
We're going to spend a couple of days of
my life. There is a lot of cleaning and
some small things that I need to get
done. And you know, we're just going to
go on this journey. What the am I even
saying? I'm like, we're just going to go
on this journey together. Like I'm going
through something emotional right now.
No, we're emotionally going to go
through this vlog together though.
That's what we are going to do. And you
know, and sometimes I'll be watching
other people's vlogs and I'm just like,
okay, like why is there 6 minutes of
like no talking? like there's 6 minutes
and it's just like them doing mundane
task and it's 6 [music] minutes of
footage and I'm like okay like is this
how I'm I'm supposed to start a vlog you
know but also who made the rules it's
not a democracy on this Now,
I'm going to do like very light makeup
today because I want to
Maybe like a little blush.
I think it's cute. I think I'm going to
put my hair back to try to get it out of
my face a little bit. So, there are a
couple things that we kind of need to
get done today. It's Sunday, so I do
need to stop by the grocery store. I
miss having a bit of fresh produce. My
nutrition has been really, really good.
However, I do feel like I want to start
incorporating a lot more veggies and
stuff. It just depends on the season of
life I'm in. It's not that I have
anything against vegetables. It's just
having to prep the veggie. I'm just
like, uh, I can't be bothered. I can't
be bothered, but I want to have a meal
filled with tons of nutrients [music]
and beautiful vitamin A and vitamin B
and D and C and F and G and ACD E F and
Z. That's what I want. How's that look
from back? If it looks bad from back,
don't tell me because what's going on in
the back? It's none of my business. It
never was. We're also going to do a
little bit of laundry today. I'm excited
because I'm going to show you guys a bit
of the decorating. I want to be able to
put up finally this piece of artwork
that I have. I also want to do this
staining thing with my pendant lamp
because like she's not giving what she
needs to give anymore. Do you know what
I mean? So, I need her to have a tan.
So, I'm excited about that. Do a little
bit of cooking and prepping. Not too
much just because like I can't be with
like the full set out meal prep. So,
I've been doing very very lazy meals,
but it does in fact get the job done and
that's what matters to me. Let's just
like reset a little bit. You know, take
it in. throwing it at you. Okay, throw
it back. Thank you. I don't know why I'm
doing that. Sorry. I just watched that
video back. The back does in fact look
crazy. And unfortunately, I'm not going
to do anything about it.
You know what they say, a kiwi a day
doesn't make the go away. Okay, but if
you're struggling with bloating, a
little kiwi action would never hurt.
Okay, little fiber. Okay, a little fiber
never hurt anyone. There's fiber inside
of these eggs as well on those yolks.
Dude, kiwis are so good. Honestly, I
think like lchi and kiwi are probably
like my favorite fruits. They're just so
like uniquely their own. Like you eat a
kiwi or you eat some lychi and like
there's nothing else that tastes like
it. You know melon like melon tastes
like melon. You know what I mean? Like
there's so many apples that taste like
other apples. But a lyche like that's a
distinct ass flavor. What am I even
talking [clears throat] about? I'm just
rambling guys. This is just like a small
breakfast. I have 23 g of protein in
[music] here. I don't like to typically
do the oo, but I couldn't get the
filler. So this is what we're
substituting for the day. I'm going to
go pick some more of the filler ones up
today cuz those are like 20 g of
protein. 100 cows like and it's just
like drinkable Greek yogurt. Like there
aren't a ton of extra ingredients
whereas in this one there is and we are
like not really pro [music]
extra processed. There are going to be
things that I eat that are processed,
but like I'm going to try and minimize
it to whole foods as much as possible
because genuinely that is what's helped
my journey so much and also like my
stomach doesn't hurt as much and I just
feel better about life. I'm also going
to do [music] two eggs. I'm going to do
my best to eat the yolks. Sometimes I
just don't be [\h__\h] with the yolks,
dude. Like I'm like this isn't good. I
feel forced. Like, don't force me to eat
this. And it's like literally just me.
Yeah,
I'm just going to quickly do my laundry.
I'm going to quickly do that. So, I
mean, I've been doing pretty good about
putting my clothes away. And honestly,
saying that even sounded like a lie, cuz
low key, it is kind of a lie. I hang a
lot of my clothes on a drying rack, you
know, and sometimes it takes a day or
two for it to dry. And then by that
point, it's the end of the week. We are
going to get to it today. I promise. Cuz
I I'm going to make that PROMISE TO
MYSELF. I CAN DO THIS. SORRY. THIS WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE A CALM VLOG. My bad.
You know, I genuinely thought that I was
going to change my sheets like to this
other duvet cover that I have had for a
while. I can't find the sheets. And I
can't find the kill and what? And I
can't find the pillow cases. And I can't
find pillowcases. Yeah. So, I just spent
the past 15 minutes searching for the
rest of this set and I can't find it.
And I'm pissed off. I'm angry. That
seems like something maybe I might do.
Smart me might do. Smart me didn't do
that. Okay, great. We're just going to
move on.
Okay, so I quickly put on like clothes
that weren't my PJs because we don't
wear paj. What is going on with my
speech right now? We don't wear PJs
outside of the house. If Hampton
University taught me one thing, it was
that. Shout out to the HU Pirates. I
definitely haven't been in the hugest
mood to wear like real clothes at the
moment. I'm just tired. I'm like
entering into my ludial phase. I'm not
feeling great. So, I'm in a sweats
deficit at the moment. So, what I'm
going to do cuz I know we're looking
This shirt, by the way, cuz I know you
guys are going to ask me. This is from
Aritzia. It's actually incredibly
flattering. The only lighting lighting
bring it back. Bring it back. Bring it
back. The only thing that pisses me off
is that I literally washed it and like
in washing it, I got like this little
stain. So, is what it is. These
sweatpants are clearly too large because
they are an XL. And if I want the
oversized look, I just don't need to do
an XL anymore. I only need to do a
large. So, these are kind of sliding off
my hip a bit. But, I'm going to put
these hair ties at the bottom of them.
And I'm going to like flip it in cuz I
kind of want to do like a really lax
looking jogger look. And I saw this
chick called Eevee Pennington.
Pennington. She did something like this
with a cute little flip-flop. Can you
guys see what's going on? I can't see
the camera in the back. I can't see at
all cuz it's a camera. Hopefully this
looks okay. I'm going to do the other
side real quick. Yeah, there we go. That
way I don't have to to keep cutting my
pants, you know, cuz I was really going
through a phase where I was just taking
scissors to everything. Not that that's
a problem. And I wasn't taking scissors
to everything. [music] Okay, I was going
to make a suicide joke, but that's not
really that funny. So, no offense. I
think I'm actually even going to switch
cameras. Do you guys want me to switch?
Like I be Do you guys care if I switch
cameras? Like the quality just switches
up randomly. No feedback from the
audience, right? Okay, I forgot this is
a dictatorship. Okay, it's not a
democracy over here. I'm going to give
what you get. Okay, wait. I'm back. What
if we did a bandana with it, right?
Like, what if I was just like, "Oh,
cute, casual. Add the bandana." I know
you guys like this. A few times I've
brought this out, you guys have been
very pleased. My thing is is like, do I
want to wear it like, you know, do I
want to wear it like Little Girl in the
Prairie or do I want to wear it like a
thug? Is it okay if I make a joke about
Crypts and Bloods or is that like not
like a no-go? Can someone in Cali like
let me know? Can I make a joke and it
not be an issue? Or have I marked
myself? Because I can go grab the blue
one and kind of not segregate it a bit,
you know, like make it seem more like
unity, but I'm I'm just not sure. I'm
just I'm really not sure. Before I put
this on, though, this Josie Moran body
butter, I've talked about it so many
times and I'm shocked that I'm like
struggling to get on that PR list. It's
so good. There's like argan oil in it.
There's other I mean, I guess I should
read it, right? It's a whipped argan oil
body butter. I thought there would be
there'd be more of a descriptor on
there, but there's not. I don't I'm all
in for just being moisturized. One of
the other ones I've been using as well
has been this Soul Day Janeiro one. Can
you guys see? Are you going to focus?
Are you going to focus? Are you going to
focus? Yeah, this Soul de Janeiro body
butter.
Sorry. I've been doing that one a lot
too like after the shower. But the only
thing I don't like about it as much is
that [music] it's like really the scent
is just like it's really strong. Like
and some people are going to really like
that. Like my best friend, no Tino, no
shade, but my best friend would love
something like that. And it's like one
of those things where it's like to eat
your own. And it's not my each or my
own. I'm more of like the only way that
you'd really smell me that much is if
you gave me [music] a nice hug. I don't
know. I just don't like people choking
on my scent. It's just not my vibe. I
was going to put this on. This is the
Oio body oil. If you've never tried
this, this stuff is actually incredible.
I worked with them on a partnership like
months back and when they sent me the
products I could try at first. The way
that I was blown away, I was like, I
think you will forever be in the lineup.
I'm not going to put that on though
because I walked outside a couple
seconds ago and it is incredibly like
humid. Like it's been so humid out here
in Florida that it like makes me want to
like throw myself off a cliff and it's
crazy cuz I'm just like you wonder why
like people don't like to wear wigs out
here. It's because like there's no point
in putting pin curls in them, right?
There's no blowouts you can do. There's
[music] no bombshell you could be unless
your hair is naturally curly and is okay
with humidity or straighter in braids
and straight like your hair has to
naturally be straight, you know? Okay,
bandana time. I don't know. I really
like that word. I haven't used it. Like,
whoever came up with that word bandanna,
I fear you did your big one, king or
queen. Queen, you did your big one,
queen. Even if it's a guy, you did your
big one. And so, instead of trying to
tuck it back in, I'm just going to cut
it cuz I like to live life dangerously.
Like, you said I cut that like too
short. I feel like these should be like
a little bit more, too.
Yeah, like we could go get a little
shorter.
Okay. Like, how do we feel about that?
Like, is it cute? Sorry. I don't know
what I'm doing that for. You guys don't
like it. That's what this is. That's why
I haven't heard you guys give me any
feedback. You don't like it. That's
okay. I'm committing to it.
I got my grocery bag because on this
channel, we don't with plasties unless
they're tits. Sorry. I just wanted to
make a joke about my boots being fake.
Okay, dude. It's so hot. By hot, I just
mean it's like really humid and it just
feels so nasty out. This is not
sponsored. [music]
I just really like this. And you guys,
like I'm a Shirley Temple freak.
Something about a Shirley Temple [music]
is going to make me filthy. Okay, feel.
And the reason for that, let me give you
guys a little bit more insight about my
childhood. So, my family's divorced.
Duh. If you couldn't tell already, my
family's divorced. And my dad used to
get us for the summers when I was like
for two or so years when I was a kid.
And my dad was an eligible bachelor.
Okay, if you guys have seen a picture
[music] of my dad in his age group and
in the age group of women that find
older men attractive, I guess he would
be considered a part of that. But he
would take us to the TGIF Fridays so he
could go on a date and we'd be there
with our uncle cuz my uncle used to work
at the bar at TGF Fridays. [music] And
my uncle would make me and my brother
unlimited Shirley Temples while we
played games at the bar. It was so much
fun. You know, there used to be a point
in time where like that little screen
had games. I don't know, but I've never
I haven't been in TGI Friday for like I
don't know 10 plus years. But yeah, it
just reminds me of my childhood with a
bit of of caffeine and something about
that. Even though like I don't know,
it's nostalgic and low key kind of makes
me sad when I think back on it. I've
been so emotional like what is going on?
Well, I do know what's going on is that
like I'm PMSing and I don't know if my
PMSing is like getting worse the older I
get or if I'm just recognizing that it's
PMSing [music] and like I'm letting
myself like fully be in it now. Do you
know what I mean? I wasn't someone that
ever cried. I was never someone that sat
there and boohooed [music] or knew or or
did any of that thing because I used to
think that crying was like a weak thing.
And it's because like that's another
story. That's a longer story. It was
literally feelings that I felt towards
my stepdad at the time because we had a
strange relationship and he was a crier.
And so when I saw him cry like it made
me not like people that cried. That's
something that I've already dealt with
in my [music] inner. Okay. Now I'm
getting hyper emotional about my youth.
And I'm still young. I'm not saying that
like and I'm not saying 30's not young.
I'm not saying 40 is not young because
imagine if you're [music] 40 and you
live to 100. That's 60 more years. You
haven't even lived half your life, which
is insane [music] to think about. It's
not that I think that I'm not young
anymore. I'm like recognizing that my
life is like passing by. And not in like
a I'm going to die way, but like in a
you know, I'm would be considered the
older co-orker at my job. Like I
remember I used to be the youngest when
I was working at Chick-fil-A, not
Chick-fil-A, when I was [music] working
at Chipotle or Olive Garden. And then
all of a sudden when I was 22, 23,
[music] I was now the oldest at that
workplace, like one of the oldest. Now
that I'm 26, you know, they're doing all
these reboots [music] like 13 Going on
30 and like they're, you know, rebooting
Camp Rock with a new cast [music] and
the Cheetah Girls and all this stuff.
And I'm just like, oh my god, like I am
aging out of what used to be my
childhood. And it makes [music] me so
sad. I don't know if that makes any
sense. It just makes me really sad. And
I feel like I've been dealing with it in
a normal way. I'm just crying.
I've just been crying like at the gym.
Catch me with the wrong Disney [music]
Channel recap
[singing]
and you got yours. I got mine. And then
like they have like the montage of like
all the like the great [music] Disney
shows. Yeah. Like catch me with that
wrong edit. I'm balding. The only thing
that makes me wet at the gym is [music]
not my sweat, it's my tears. And my
tears are not from excessive work, it's
from sadness. I don't know. I feel like
I'm grieving. So, now that we kind of
got that weird thing out the way, we're
about to go grocery shopping. I actually
don't need that many groceries. The
reason why I don't need that many
groceries is because I've been lazy
eating. I've been lazy healthy eating.
Okay? And by healthy, I've been lazy
macro friendly eating. Okay? We say that
because I I really don't like that word
healthy. It's just not my favorite word.
Sometimes I'll use it in the thumbnails
and or like the titles, but it's just
because [music] it's SEO, like it's
searchable. But on this page, that word
in particular, it's just a lot of nuance
with it. So, I'm not going to use it for
foods. I have a lot of this stuff
already. So, the only thing that I want
to switch up, [music] and I talked about
this a little bit earlier, is that I do
want to add a couple more extra veggies,
just some micronutrients in there just
to like add a little bit more balance.
So, for breakfast, I have been doing
boiled eggs, kiwi, drinkable Greek
yogurt, and some protein waffles. Now,
again, like the Kodiak [music] protein
waffles, anything that is listed as high
protein, this high protein that, and
it's something that's highly processed,
I'm really not a fan of. However,
[music] in this moment, I'm just not
going to give a, right? It is practice
what you preach. And for most of the
things that I consume, I live that
truth. Okay? But for those waffles at
the moment, I'm not living [music] that
truth. So, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to let those kind of die out. I
think I have about [music] a couple more
days worth of them. And then I'm going
to reintroduce sourdough bread back into
my diet. And I want it to be like a high
protein option, like [music] another cuz
I think it's like 16 g of protein from
those waffles. So, I want to introduce
something that's also going to bring me
back a little bit more in there. But I
could just do eggs [music] and cheese. I
could just do eggs and cheese. I haven't
really done cheese in a minute. I think
in my head I'm just like, oh, like if I
do cheese, like it has to be like
scramble my eggs or something. I'm like,
I guess I could just cut a slice of
cheese. Do you know what I mean? It's
not going to be 16 g, but it could be
seven and a wins win. So, yeah, that's
what breakfast is looking at.
Pre-workout snack, I'm doing musli,
which you guys have seen the evolution
of my pre-workout snacks. If you've been
with this channel for a while, you
follow me on short form content, but
like you know, it went from being one of
these things where I was like, "Yeah,
like we love the rice cakes with honey
and salt and then it transitioned
[music]
into Cheerios and then it transitioned
into dates with honey and then it
transitioned like there was a period of
time where I tried to do a Rice Krispie
treat. [music] I just don't like the way
that tastes." It was this protein cereal
that I got at Whole Foods and now we
were at Musli which are just like oats
and stuff. It's just like oats and I
really like it right now. I've been
having it with lactose-free milk,
particularly the Fairlife milk, just
because there is some extra protein in
there. And I'll do like the fat-ree one
or the 2%. And then that's my
pre-workout snack. Post-workout snack, I
have not been doing any more protein
shakes or any more protein bars. I'm
done with them. Unless I have to, I'm
done with them. They just started to
taste. And I I love Built [music] Bars,
but I'm telling you, like it got to a
point where I was eating it and I was
like, what the You know, you start
chewing something and it just doesn't
taste right. Like it doesn't taste like
it should taste like that. Like that's
where I was at. So yeah, like I can't
eat those anymore. Like I'm done. I
can't eat them anymore. And stuff like
that. Again, it just like if you're
wondering why you're like bloating and
your stomach [music] is hurt and your
nothing's digesting right cuz the older
you get, this will get worse. Some
people are very lucky, some very far in
between, but [music] the older you get
this will get worse. Okay. My
sensitivity to food has gone out the
roof. is something that makes it really
really easy for me to not [music] eat
fast food is that now when I eat it
because I'm so consistent with eating a
lot of whole foods and balanced meals
when I eat fast food [music] like fries
or something like that do my stomach
hurts bad. My stomach hurts really
really bad. Okay. Or like I had like a
Chick-fil-A meal with my dad when I went
to go visit him and as soon as [music] I
ate it dude was like I knocked out on my
couch and I'm like food should not be
making you feel like that, right? Like
you shouldn't feel instantly drowsy and
tired [music] after eating a meal. Like
that's not normal. So yeah, like it's
easy. Or like I'll have Wings Stop and
[music] I'm like, "Okay, like yeah, like
cheat meal or you know, or like not even
a cheat meal, like you know, I'm going
to eat [music] this." And I eat it and
again like I feel like crap. I feel
gross. I feel heavy [music] and like I'm
really really happy that like I'm at
that point now because it makes it
really really easy to not continue to
keep [music] gravitating towards those
things. And I think it's something that
genuinely only comes with time. And the
longer and the more consistently that
you are eating those whole foods because
then it starts reminding you again, we
should not be eating this like
McDonald's. I actually like and never
say never of course. [music] I don't
think I'm ever going to go back there. I
don't think I'm ever going to go back to
McDonald's unless someone brings me a
hash brown. But if that's not the case,
I don't think [music] I'm ever going
back there. I'm not placing judgment on
anyone. Like if you love McDonald's, I
love that you love McDonald's. Okay?
There was a point in time that I really
like Moe's queso. I used to be able to
[music] eat the 12 box taco from Taco
Bell. All of them. All 12. Crunchy sour
cream. [music] Supreme loaded. But now I
can't even imagine it. I can't imagine
it because this food, it's like the
quality of the food is getting worse. Or
maybe my palette is getting a little bit
more particular. Either way, like it's
done. Like I'm done. Now for lunch and
dinner, [music] I've been having the
exact same thing. I've been doing
literally tuna, rice, some crispy
seaweed on the side, half an avocado for
some healthy fats in there. [music] I'll
season the tuna with rice wine vinegar
and like some biyak seasoning. [music]
And that oh that has been doing me
wonders. Someone in my comments
recommended that I add some pickled
onions to it and some [music] tomatoes.
So that's what I'm going to do this week
because I do think it's going to be
really really tasty. The beautiful thing
about that type of meal prepping or that
type of food is that if you don't grab
the tuna pack from the store and call it
a day and then you only really need to
cook the rice and you can cook the rice
in bulk. You know, I cook the rice for
like 3 days at a time and that way I
don't have to worry about feeling
overwhelmed or stressed. And I know some
of you guys again are going to be like,
"Oh, I can't eat the same thing over and
over again." I get that. Like you can't
eat the same thing over and over again
when you don't really like it, right? So
now the goal for you would be to then
find something that you really like and
that's going to take time to figure out.
I mean, if you guys have been on my page
for a while, you know that I have done
so many random meal preps and some of
them lasted a really long time. There
was a point where I was having a beefogi
bowl for lunch and dinner, just like I'm
having this tuna bowl for lunch and
dinner literally every day for a year.
And then there's going to be times
where, you know, I did like a lasagna
soup or I did like spaghetti. [music] I
did like Greek meatballs. Those are
really good though, you know, where it
just didn't stick as much. It just
didn't hit the same. [music] So, you'll
have to figure some things out. And in
that, you'll have to waste some time and
you'll probably have to waste a little
bit of money on ingredients. But once
you figure it out, like stick with it
and just see what it does, right? A lot
of you guys are asking [music] me or
pointing out on my comments like,
"What's the secret? What's the secret?"
The secret is that the skills that I've
been telling you for the past 4 years,
not four [music] years, are we at 4
years? No, I started YouTube. For the
past 3 years, the skills that I have
been sharing with you guys, I'm finally
at a point where I have been able
[music] to continue to be consistent and
replicate these skills over and over and
over again. Fitness is like [music] a
sport, okay? It's a sport. It's a sport
that you have to practice. You have to
practice being good at these skills,
right? The skill isn't knowing how to do
it. The skill is being able to execute
it over and over and over again. [music]
You know, I'll give you another example.
I know this is such a long yap. I'm
sorry if I'm like boring you guys. I'll
give you another example. Like one of my
girlfriends invited me out [music] to go
have a trauma dump ice cream date and I
went with her and usually I would go in
there and I'm like, "Okay, like let me
get all the extra [music] toppings. Let
me do all of this. Let me get a com, you
know, let me do the works, right? Like
if I'm going in here because, you know,
I love to have a great [music] time with
ice cream. Ice cream is like my favorite
dessert. Instead of getting two, three
scoops of ice cream. I did one scoop. I
I tasted some of [music] them. I didn't
finish the taster because you don't need
to do that, especially if you don't even
like the flavor [music] that much. And I
got one scoop and I got sprinkles. I
told myself that, especially because
like again, it's out the blue. It wasn't
something that I was planning on doing.
I told myself [music] that I could get a
scoop of ice cream and one topping of my
choice. And I got a scoop of ice cream.
It [music] was like this really tasty
banana kind of bananas fosters dolce de
leche ice cream flavor. I got it in a
waffle cone and I got these delicious
ube sprinkles on it [music] and I ate
the whole thing and it was so good. And
after I was done eating the whole thing
I was like oh wait like I'm actually sat
like I'm fully satisfied with this
because the other half of me would have
been like oh but like I also kind of
like this flavor too so I should get
both flavors. But like I would have just
forced myself to finish it because I
[music] got both even though deep down I
knew that I didn't need both. And it's
about literally listening to your body
and asking yourself how do [music] you
actually feel? Like do I feel okay? like
am I eating this for the sake of eating
it? That's why I'm like so against
having for me personally and that's also
because I have a binge eating disorder
or I've suffered I don't want to say
I've suffer I've suffered a lot worse
than I do now. I haven't binged [music]
in so long thank God with binge eating
disorder. And so having a lot of snacks
that like are not a part of my plan at
home for the sake of having them. It
it's okay when I'm having a good week,
but when [music] I'm not having a good
week or maybe when I'm extra cravy or
anything like that like and those snacks
are available to me. I personally do not
have enough strength to tell [music]
myself no in the moment. Okay? It's
something that I'll be like thinking
over and over and over again. It's the
only thing I'm thinking on my mind. I'm
only thinking [music] be disciplined.
Say no, don't eat it. I don't have to do
any of that if it's not in the house.
Okay? So, the snacks that I keep in my
house support the plan, support the
goal. Okay? So, whether [music] that's
maybe some little cutie pie oranges or
like kiwis or like I'll have some frozen
fruit or like an outshine pops in the
freezer. I really like fruit riot. Like
that's what I've been having at the end
of the night. It's like a cute little
fruit dessert. I love it. You know, like
nobody wants to binge eat beef sticks.
Like nobody wants to do that. Like
that's not [music] hitting it. But I
promise you when your back is against
the wall and the only thing you have to
pick is a beef stick and you eat it and
you're just like I actually was never
really that hungry. [music] And the
protein also helped as well. Protein and
fiber as well. So yeah. So that's kind
of what I'm eating right now. I [music]
also have some fish in my freezer as
well that I could always switch in and
some broccoli as well that I could
switch in [music] for like the tuna. But
like right now I'm just kind of on this
tuna kick. So, I'm going to write that
out until it gets bored and then I'm
going to go back on my fish cake. And
then who knows, maybe I'll start
bringing back chicken or beef. I'm just
like I'm beefed out, y'all. Like, there
was a point in [music] time where I was
eating beef lunch, dinner, lunch,
dinner, and I was even having beef
bacon. You got to chill. My heart needed
to chill. Now I got the beef ick. I
don't want to have the beef ick. That
was like a super long chat, but also I
think it was needed. Like sometimes we
kind of just need to have like candid
moments together. [music] Yeah. Like
intimaty moments. Also, like do you guys
like the longer vlogs? Like [music] I
remember there was a point in time where
I would literally be vlogging and the
whole episode would be 12 minutes. Like
is that an issue? Like what's our
problem here? Cuz I know a lot of you
guys have been begging for longer vlogs.
I've been giving it to and I feel like
I've been getting really really good
[music] feedback from it. But you know
also like I don't know like if I if I'm
yapping too much like I'll stop cuz like
doing a vlog that's an hour long or 40
minutes that is a lot of work. Okay. I
want you guys to pull the camera up
[music] one day. I want you to pull a
camera up and I want you to try and
speak for 40 minutes straight. It's not
easy. So, I just want to make sure that
I'm I'm doing what you guys want. Next
week's video is going to be centered
around a topic because the goal for me
is to get one of those videos out a
month and then three weekly vlogs since
[music] you guys happen to really like
this mundane, boring that I'm doing.
[laughter]
Okay. Yeah, let's grocery shop. Okay.
[music] So, I actually like got to the
grocery store, but I'm realizing right
now I did not put on any deodorant. But
you want to know what I keep in my car?
Deodorant. Because that's what the
prepared giries do. Okay? I keep this in
my car and I keep this in my car because
bad can't digest lactose. I'm not like a
super huge fan of like natural
deodorants, but Salt and Stone like
doesn't make me smell like a goddamn
armpit when I use [music] it. So, not
mad at her. All right, let's go.
Yeah. So, one of the thing that I love
the most about Whole Foods is that they
just have fresh veggies, fresh cuts, and
you don't really have to like question
it as much cuz, you know, like there's
like lowkey like a standard [music] to
be able to put your food in the grocery
store. Do you know what I mean? But I
also could be wrong, right? This [music]
could be like elitist thinking and I'm
being brainwashed and thinking that
that's okay and it's not. I don't know.
Yeah, I'm actually not going to get any
of this. Low key though, I wouldn't be
mad at having like a fresh pressed juice
in the morning, but like I have a juicer
at home and I do love me some pear and
cucumber juice. Good tea. I've never
juiced anything. Like I don't know what
else I need. It might just be that
though. Okay, so when it comes to
picking out avocados, typically you're
going to want like some of the dark like
these are too soft. Like they're not
going to last throughout the week. So I
like to find one that's like still
pretty green and firm. That way it
doesn't get like all nasty because
unfortunately I do discriminate against
dark avocados and it didn't even have to
be that they're dark dark. You know if
they if when they were right they were
dark then like I wouldn't be
discriminating against [music] it being
dark. You get what I'm saying? Maybe you
don't get what I'm saying. Maybe I'm
dumb as like yeah. You see this one?
It's like kind of green still. It's a
little bit soft but it's not that bad.
And it's so funny because I genuinely
used to be someone that like did not
with avocados. Like I did not like it. I
did not understand the hype of it when
it became a thing. [music] And now,
like, I feel like I can't eat any of my
dinner meals without an avocado because
the flavor and the texture that it just
adds is immaculate. I'm thinking about
adding some berries with my breakfast.
Berries are amazing. They're great
fiber. I'm already having a good with
it, but don't mind adding a little bit
more.
You guys, I have never had an urge to
juice [music] something, but I think I'm
going to juice. Like, I think I'm going
to be one of those juicing
cuz like [music] why not? Going to grab
some kiwis. So technically the green
kiwis have a little bit more fiber than
the golden kiwis. Even though I like
golden ones better, but I'm here for
that fiber. I actually don't know how to
tell the difference of whether or not
like [music] which kiwis are good or
not. I just am grabbing the box and
hoping that I get a good bunch. Okay,
now I don't have like any specialty
pairs that I with. So I'm just going to
grab ones that don't look like they're
too bruised up. But also like maybe I do
want the really bruised ones
juicing it. I'm only going to get two.
This is my first time. I'm going to have
a hard time juicing this. Whatever.
Guess we'll find out. Okay. Like I'm
actually [music] a huge freaking tomato.
I know a lot of people don't tomatoes
and I really don't get that. I think
it's weird. I think it's weird when you
[music] don't like tomatoes cuz to me
like that adds just like a bomb of
flavor and a little bit of citrus and
love, but [music] some people obviously
think it's a goddamn hat crime to add
tomatoes to things. My My bestie doesn't
like tomatoes. My brother's a great
example of someone that doesn't like
tomatoes. [music] Weird. My bestie is
not weird. I mean, she's weird, but like
I like it. I'm also like someone that
likes to keep things like on the stem.
Like I wasn't always like this, but my
partner's kind of got me more on that
realm. I am someone that is going to
with some Tai Chasm rice every goddamn
day. I don't know, something about it
just feels very fragrant. Feels [music]
very culturally appropriated in the best
way. And usually I don't have to ever
get rice, but I've actually used it all.
So, win's a win. They also have this
really, really tasty Lii seasoning
sauce. So, like when I do finally go
back to doing fish, like I should
probably grab it now. That way I don't
have to like want to off myself.
I mean, does someone want to tell me
what the [\h__\h] difference between
extra sharp cheddar and it's yellow and
extra sharp cheddar and it's white?
Like, I need to know. I just like my
cheddar like crispy as. Does that make
any sense?
Okay, that was a pretty successful trip
to the grocery store. And honestly, that
wasn't as expensive as it usually is,
but also I didn't find any meat, so you
never
know. Did you guys like the grocery
store bit? I'm a little insecure about
it. I don't know. Sometimes I get
uncomfortable in there like talking, but
also like no one cares. Like nobody
cares. Cuz I know a lot of you guys have
been like, "Oh, like how are you not
uncomfortable like on the phone like or
like filming in public?" Like I mean I
don't know. I feel like I am. I was just
being an honest woman. I'm definitely an
honest woman [music] if you know what I
mean. High key. I need to go into
Sephora, but I don't think I'm going to
take y'all with me because this little
guy is [music] Maybe I will take you
guys with me. I'm going to let her
charge up a bit.
Dude, I'm a girl that loves a funky
cheese. Mhm. If my cheese doesn't have
personality, like I don't want it. Like
that's how I feel about Swiss. Like I
feel like Swiss cheese I'm like, "Oh,
you look like you got personality."
Swiss cheese is like a hot person with
no personality. You're like, "Oh, you're
so hot." And you talk to them, and
there's no substance. I want like a
cheddar. You know what I mean? I want
like some Gouda. I want some havari. I
want some goat cheese. You know, looks
plain, but it's like love in your mouth.
M. I should probably take that lactase
inside because we're not slow. If I want
to enjoy the cheeses, I have to just be
wise about it. You know, life is better
when you take a lactate. Unsponsored.
Weird. I'm going through like a weird
cheese craving. What's going on with
that? And I can't be pregnant. I haven't
been having intercourse because I'm long
distance and I got a full bear bush down
there. Am I going [music] to Joe and the
Juice and Sephora? Yeah. Yeah, maybe I
am. I love Joe and the Juice, but not in
the same way that other people love Joe
and the Juice, right? [music] Like I
love Joe and the Juice because Jesus
Christ, I was about to say something so
goddamn basic. Don't do not listen
[music] to me. Please don't listen to
me. I'm being insufferable. I'm being
insufferable. There's like no parking. I
should have just stayed at my parking
spot and walked my ass over here, but
no, I didn't.
So, like I'm talking really low.
Hopefully you guys can hear me, but the
two young women next to me are like talk
like I think they're in high school or
something, but they're kind of talking.
And the way that [music] I'm like
incredibly invested is like a problem.
Do you guys like ease drop on people?
Like, is it of me to do that? Like, I
need to know. Also, I mean, like, is it
of me to do that? Yes or no? Like, it
doesn't matter cuz I'm not going to stop
doing it. And see, and that's why I
understand why [clears throat] people in
the UK love American sometimes because
like we do just be laying it all out in
public spaces and we kind of don't care.
And it's like it was quiet on the tube.
Now [music] it's not quiet on the tube.
Now I'm listening to a story about how
your ex cheated on you. I don't know.
Like I'm here for it. And the lady who
freaking took my order was so nice. She
gave me such a compliment. And then
listen, the best thing that you can do
whenever someone gives you a compliment,
like when I receive that energy, I like
to give that energy right back. take it
[music] in and then push it out. You
know, it's kind of like if I was the
avatar, like that would be my example
being an avatar. Okay, that that would
be my power is trying to uplift women
that try to uplift other women. So, when
someone gives you a compliment, you take
it and you say, "Thank you." [music] And
then you say, "But look who's talking."
Okay. Oh my god, you're so beautiful.
Thank you. Look who's talking. I love
doing that because I think it's just
such a beautiful way to to, like I said,
like bring that energy in and and push
it back out in the best way. This is my
version of a dad joke. Okay. Oh, that's
my sandwich. That's my sandwich.
Can we take a moment for this? Like,
look at that. Can we take a goddamn
moment for this? Like, it's incredible.
And it's like 34 g of protein, around
500 calories. Like, we're not mad at
her. And it's funny because when I first
started my finish train, I used to hear
500 calories, and I was like, "Oh my
god, like that's so many calories."
Like, that's not cuz think about it like
this. If you're having, let's say, three
larger meals a day and three of those
meals that's 500 calories. That's only
1,500 calories, right? Most of us are
eating over 1500 calories. You know, the
daily recommended value for the average
healthy individual is around 2,000
calories. That means you got 500
calories left of snacks. When you think
about it like that, that's ideal. That's
ideal.
Oh my god. When I tell you that that
sandwich just [music] like changed my
goddamn life, like I feel happy. We're
in Sephora. I'm sorry. I know. I said I
was going to go, but I lied.
Okay, so you can't film in Sephora. I
didn't know that. Is that something that
I mean, I guess I wouldn't know that cuz
I don't typically film in Sephora. Well,
I thought I would give us a little
Sephora haul. Sephora?
I love being a girl. I mean, you don't
have to be a girl to go in there. I saw
a guy in there with a hoodie on. He
looked a little suspicious. I was like,
what are you doing? You don't want
people to know you're in here? Cuz
there's no shame in here. Like, we don't
care. were shamefully in here as well.
So, what I'm really trying to find is a
lip product that is a little bit more
taupeish color, but like a black girl
taupe. [music] And as you can see here,
I have quite literally put so many
different colors on my arms. Like,
[music] I've put I've put so many. So,
I've narrowed it down to a couple, but
honestly, we won't really know unless I
put it on my lips. And we will
experiment with that tomorrow morning.
So, I got the Mighty Fine Brow Pen. So,
I had the L'Oreal Faux Brow, which I
really liked. However, the only thing I
did not like about it was that the lid
would not stay on. I'm not going to
fight you on this. Like, stay the on.
Like, I'm not about to sit here and
force you. It's like being a personal
trainer. I'm going to want it for you,
but you also have to want it. If you
need help during your fitness journey, I
offer one-on-one coaching applications
in my bio. So, I picked this one up.
It's a very similar where it has like
[music] the fine tips and it's supposed
to look like little hairs and stuff. I
tried out a couple of different colors.
cuz I ended up getting 4.5 neutral deep
brown. I can't go too warm on my hair
color. And then I also picked up an
Hourglass
Volumizing Glossy Balm in the color
lure.
Now, I actually already have this. I'm
going to show you. I don't have it in
this color, though. I picked up another
color. I actually really, really enjoy
the formula of that. I say I pick it up
in another color, not in the bag. It's
got to be in the purse, though. So, I
definitely actively remember this being
in here. Yes. Here we go. So, the
current color that I have is impulse.
This is what the color looks like. I had
another color as well, and it was more
like a just I guess I'll show you my
finger, but it's a really pretty color.
It's really pretty. The thing that I
like the most about it is the formula. I
think the formula is really nice. I wish
there was more product in here, though,
because, you know, I'm not really one to
like run out of lip product except for
like, you know, lip liners. Like, I'll
run out of that. But, like, with stuff
like this, I don't usually run out of.
And I I literally like was using it and
I was like pulling [music] it up and it
was empty and I was like, "Oh my god."
Like my purse. See, I picked that up and
then this scared me. I was so confused
why this was in the bag. She must have
just shoved that in the bag. I didn't
see that. I picked up the say
lightweight setting spray. I heard
really really good reviews of this. I'm
[music] big on like I I need a setting
spray. Like you can't just work. You
also have to have a good spray. The
hooded beauty spray is like freaking
great. The product is great. The nozzle
is horrible. And I need her to fix that
ASAP. [music] Okay. in a respectful
criticism way, not in a I don't like the
product way. The product is really good,
but I can't keep using it if I'm having
to fight for my life to get it out the
bottle. And then when it does get out my
bottle, it's like spitting on me, like,
you know, it's not like a nice mist,
it's spitting. So, I heard this one has
like a really, really good mist, which
[music] I'm excited about. And then I
picked up my OG lip liner that I love.
This is the color John from Kofi. The
lip liner stains, so that's why I really
like it. And then this is where we're
kind of get into it a bit with these two
colors. So, I got Makeup Forever. Now, I
love Makeup Forever Limitless Brown.
Like, that's my baby. That's my tea.
But, I wanted to try again like [music]
more of the top shade. So, I bought two
of the shades cuz I'm just going to have
to see how it lays on my [music] lips.
Now, when I was using a more taupish
shade before, I have used Stretch from
Road, but that is like sold out for the
rest of my life. Like, I can't get my
hands on it. I can't get it online and I
can't get it in store. So, I'm just
annoyed about that. So, I'm hoping that
these two will do the job. So, yay. I'm
excited about that. And that's my haul.
Okay, that's my haul, you guys. I just
had the craziest interaction with a
homeless guy. I typically don't give to
like homeless like men. Like typically I
don't It's not that I have anything
against men. This is no shade, no
[music] disrespect at all to anyone,
okay? But I definitely don't typically
help white homeless men. Don't usually
do that. Just cuz, you know, obviously
everyone's situation's different. But if
I am going to be generous, I do keep
water and like snacks back here. So like
when I see the homeless, I can give him
some snacks cuz I don't carry cash
anymore. But this white guy, he was
like, "Can you give me a dollar?" I was
like, "I don't have a dollar." He's
like, "Well, can you get me a coffee?"
And I was like, "I guess I could get you
a coffee." So I got him a coffee. I hand
him the drink. I see one of the people
that lives in my building and I'm
talking to him. You know, I make a joke
[music] cuz I he had messaged me and I
didn't respond back. But like I I
responded back and then he messaged me
and then I didn't respond back. But like
you guys, like if you get a response
from me ever, if you if you get a
response from me from the comments, from
the DMs, from texts, anything like that,
you got me in a great moment because
when I tell you that my mental health
like does not like let me do that often.
Okay, so I was talking to I was like,
"Yeah, like you know, I was kind of
fighting for my life." He's like, "The
homeless guy chimes in. He chimes in."
He's like, "Oh yeah, like don't kill
yourself. I tried to slit my own throat
and I didn't die." First off, you know,
let me say this real quick and not to be
insensitive. if you're going to, you
know, [\h__\h] there has to be a certain
amount of like just off like off up here
to choose to do it by slitting your own
throat. Like that's that's crazy to me.
Like that's I'm like wait you you okay
like you know and they were like like
you did that to [music] yourself and
then for him to be like oh yeah like it
didn't work and like if you shoot
yourself in the head like you might
survive [music] it and so like I made a
joke and I was like okay like yeah like
you know I guess I won't go that that
[music] route. you know, if I survive a
shot in the head when I wake up, I'll be
going for the second attempt. And
honestly, for some people that don't
understand that type of humor, like,
you're going to be offended by that, and
that's fair. That's I got to I got to
own up to that. But like, I don't know.
The interaction was just so weird. I was
like, you could have just took your
coffee and move on. But now you're
telling me which routes not to take with
not trying to wake up the next day. So,
yeah, that's how that went. Okay. Yeah.
Like, that was great.
Sorry, I just wanted to do that. I
looked in the mirror. I took the most
massive poop or this morning. It was
delectable. And I used wipes. It was
just a real cleanup. And then I turned
on the light. I put a face mask on last
night and I looked like Hannibal Lecter.
I look like I want five teens. Okay. The
stereotypical jock, the pthead, the
[\h__\h] the virgin nerdy girl, and the
good guy. I want them all at a farmhouse
in the middle of nowhere. And I want a
mother chainsaw,
you guys. Like first off, sleep score. I
have an ordering sleep score. Terrible.
I took an energy drink at 6:00 p.m.
because I was like, "Oh, like I really
need to clean this house, you know, for
the next day." And I didn't just want to
clean it. I wanted to declutter it. So,
I went through three full rooms. I went
through drawers. I went through clothes.
I went through big baskets full of a
whole bunch of stuff. And you guys, cuz
I'm an influencer, like, I get a whole
bunch of stuff sent to me. And I'm going
to do a giveaway. Trust me, I'm going to
do a giveaway. I'm getting everything
together. I just haven't decluttered
yet. Oh my balls, dude. I literally was
up till 1:00 a.m., but I got it done and
I deep cleaned my bathroom. Okay, a
win's a win. But the energy drink thing
by the time it came to the end of the
night, like I just wasn't sleepy, you
know? So, I slept for 3 hours and 4
minutes. And then I'm feeling this weird
vibration thing going on in my bed. I'm
really not sure what that's about. Like,
I'm on the top floor of my apartment
building and like I feel like in the
middle of the night I can feel like the
floor shaking. I'm going to say
something solid because and mark my
words if this isn't God forbid if this
is how I die in my apartment complex
like just like falls to the ground cuz
I'm on the 27th floor. I'm not making
it. [clears throat] Someone needs to sue
for me. Okay? Someone needs to sue for
me. I'm just putting that out there.
Okay? Because obviously I don't know if
you guys follow me on TikTok. I did like
a little like night chat and I was
talking about like some of my anxiety
cuz my dad is cancer. Some of my anxiety
about that is now that like I'm really
scared to die myself. So, anytime
there's turbulence, anytime like a car
drives past me too fast, anytime I'm
looking both ways, anything is slightly
off, I feel like it's a omen for me to
to not make it the next day. Like, I
don't know. My anxiety has just been a
little bit through the roof. It's
slimmed down a little bit cuz my dad has
been doing really really well. He's been
responding really positively to his
cancer treatment. My anxiety has been
less, but then like I was laying there
awake and I'm just feeling that slight
vibration of the building and I'm like,
this could be it for me. I don't know
though. I'm bowing out. That was like a
lot for many reasons, you know. I'm not
going to say for no reason because on
this page out of Moxons, [\h__\h] Let's
get ready. Wow. Do you guys see my skin?
Is it showing up? Wow. At first, I was
like, uh, wow. Now, if you guys don't
know what these masks are, they are the
Biodance mask.
Okay. From Bioance. This is the
rejuvenating caviar PRN real deep mask.
So, there's caviar water, caviar
extract, PDRN, and salmon egg extract.
But you have to keep this on your skin
for 4 hours and I kept it on the whole
night. So, PDRM for deep skin
rejuvenation infused with PDRN [music]
to support skin vitality, boosting
hydration, and glow. Yeah. Ampole. I've
never heard this word. A M P O U L E.
AOL sounds Spanish. Solidified into the
form of a hydrogel mask. Caviar for
fortified skin barrier. 58% caviar water
enhances skin condition and reveals a
healthy glow and then it turns
transparent as it's absorbed. [music] So
when I put this on it was purple. It's
still purple. It's just like transparent
purple now. Yeah. Like my skin looks
incredible now. I actually felt bad
because I got gifted this when I went to
that shoot in Miami and I was like dude
like I first put it on my skin and I was
like this is burning. You know I'm a
girl with sensitive skin so I get
nervous. Like you know I don't really
like doing too much. You know I'm real
quiet on the creek with it. I was like,
"Let me give it a second chance." Cuz
like once I realized that it wasn't
something that you keep [music] on your
face for 20 minutes and that's something
you keep on your face for 40 minutes, I
was like, "I think I'm just going to
have to fight through it." And I did.
And honestly, I'm going to do this once
a mother week because this looks
incredible. I almost feel like I don't
even need to ever do micro needling.
Like, do I rub this in? Like, I'm not
even going to wash my face. I don't
usually wash my face anyway, but I
usually do like spray some on it. Wait,
let me see if there's directions on how
to afterare this because like the gold
on my skin makes me not even want to
wear makeup. Like, I look incredible.
Hm. No postcare instructions. Bio dance.
I think you should work on that because
I really don't know what the I'm doing.
Oh my god, someone said the rudest
comment to me like, "Oh my god, it was I
mean it was kind of funny." So when
everything was like the highlight of
like life, like when I was really going
through it, everyone was making these
comments about my weight. Like people
were saying mean things like I just
wasn't open to the comments, you know,
cuz I'm like an out of sight, out of
mind person. I got to keep my peace. But
like now I'm actually like really happy
that all of that happened because like
my feelings I don't take it as personal
anymore. Like I used to see it and like
take it, oh wow, like I am ugly. I am
frail. I am annoying. You know, I used
to see something like that and and take
it like to heart or like as if it would,
you know, it's something that would like
affect me. But I have had so much growth
since freaking June that now I'm like
back to reading my comments and
responding to everyone. I just feel so
much better about it. I've been being a
little bit more vocal about it because
it actually doesn't hurt my feelings
anymore in the same way. I'm like, I'm
going to call you out if you're being
rude again. like this [\h__\h] is a
dictatorship on this page. You know,
you're going to be typing a hate comment
and I'm going to be quick [music] to
block cuz in my head I'm like, "Haha,
caught you in the middle one." To me,
like brings me a little [music] bit of
joy cuz you know, like I'm here to like
promote positivity, good vibes. I want
you to feel comfortable in your own
skin. I want you to feel comfortable
about who you are, okay? I want to
uplift you. So, what we're not going to
do is bring that negative sassy energy
back on this like there ain't going to
be consequences. Okay? I'm against
beating kids. I don't believe anyone
should be beating children. But on this
page, I'm imaginarily beating children.
You know what I mean? And the children
are people that say rude things. I'm
like, okay. Like, your mom never tell
you if you don't have anything nice to
say, keep it to yourself. You know, my
mom did and she wasn't fullying there.
If you know what I mean. You know what?
Love my mom though. Love my mom. And
that's the thing, right? Like just
because a comment isn't inherently mean
or your intent behind it isn't
inherently mean doesn't mean it's not
rude. Anyway, this comment from a man
obviously like the comments that bother
me the least are from men because it's
just like, "What are you doing here,
dude? Like, what are you even doing
here?" A guy was like, "She literally
looks dead in the face." On a video that
I posted, I was like, "Dude, like sue
me. I'm not wearing any concealer." You
guys, if my face does start to look
dead, I promise you, I'll be the first
to know because I see myself more than
the average person sees himself, okay?
With hours and hours and hours and hours
of footage for the past almost 4 years.
Once I start looking dead, I promise you
I'll know. But he said that and I was
like, dude, like I literally got PRP
micro needling under the eye. Like don't
do that. Like I have good under eye
care. Like let's not do that. But it was
just funny cuz I was like, damn. Like
men are just
Oh, guys, jawline filler update. She's
gone. I don't know if you guys noticed.
It's like a little less dark in this
area and droopy. Or maybe it's not. Or
maybe it's in my head. Maybe it looks
exactly the same.
Oh my god. Like you guys, like, let me
try to get a mirror to try to reflect on
my face. Does that look better? Oh, hold
up. Wow. Ooh. Ah, that's some good
skinincare right there. Well, let me
tell you again. I said this in my last
two videos ago. When you see people with
amazing skin, okay, that previously
didn't maybe have the best skin and
they're just like, "This skin product
changed my life." I'll only accept that
with those masks cuz that mask is really
nice. And actually, I will be buying
those from now on. And Trenno, Trennoan
changed my skin's life. Like when I tell
you that I used to have really bad acne.
And you guys, I'm ludo phase. So I have
a bit of like acne kind of popping up
here and there, but like the way Tinoan
changed my goddamn life. And yes, you do
have to go in the United States, go to a
derm and get it prescribed to you, but
it's like not hard. It's like not hard.
Like go to the derm and be like, "Hey,
this is my skincare routine." They'll be
like, "Oh, you should go on tininoan.
Here you go." And then you pick your
bottle up. I've had my tininoan. I fixed
my acne back in 2023 bad summer. In the
past three years, I've only used two
bottles of treone and I use it every
night. This what it looks like.
This container lasts you forever because
you only need P-s size amount. You're
going to put a pee on your finger and
you're going to think it's not enough.
And I'm telling you, it is enough. Okay?
Especially if you're trying to like
avoid like the dry patchy look. You're
putting too much when you get to that
point. Trust me, I know. And I would
never steer you wrong on purpose.
Now, I have both the Danessa Myrix the
water powder serum and I also have their
universal skin like blurring balm. Um, I
like this one better. I know some people
use both, but I've just been using this
one for a while cuz I was only just
using this one. And this is good. This
is what's replaced the Milk Grippy
Primer. Like, we're done with the random
sparkles on my face. I guess I'll try
this one today. Here we go.
And now if you tap the screen, it will
blend my makeup.
Oh my god. So, I haven't like set
anything yet, but yeah, like makeup came
out. Sorry, I keep looking in the
viewfinder. Like, makeup came out like
pretty decent, per se. So, you guys,
let's talk about the elephant in the
room. These these girly pods that I
bought yesterday. True Taupe and Endless
Cacao. I can confirm they are not made
for people of color. Insert photos. You
know, I'm never someone that's like
super into returning makeup, but like
absolutely not. I'm returning this. And
like there's no point in putting it on
the wrist because that would be nothing.
And then I'm also returning this brow
pencil. Unfortunately, guys, it does not
work or show up. I have wiped my brow
off. I've tried a million things. She
was not g She was giving pigment here.
She was not giving pigment on the brow.
So, yeah. I'm returning this and I don't
have any goddamn shame about it.
Normalize returning it. This is my first
time trying the say setting spray. I'm
actually really excited about this
because I posted this little haul on Tik
Tok and you guys were like, "Oh my god,
like girl, it's great. Like I love it."
Oh yeah, that's like an even mist. See,
like that's what I'm talking about. Like
can you guys see it? I need a fine
effing mist. You know, like I need a
fine mist. This is nice. I already feel
like I'm glowing more. What do you guys
think? Okay, let's talk about the lip
color that I do have on. So, I'm
actually not wearing the Kofi lip liner
today. I'm actually not wearing this
one. I'm giving this one a try again. I
was wearing that one a lot. So, and this
one was like out and I never like
resharpened it, but I resharpened it
today. This is Bittersweet from MPH, I
believe. And I saw Courtney wear this
liner and I was like, "Oh, okay. Look,
let me see. I'll buy it." Baby,
that's like the perfect like literally
like everyday lip shade. Am I wrong? Let
me go ahead and blend the edges out, you
know, for that blurry look because I
like it to look a bit blurry. But if
anything, I would say that this is more
closer to like a neutral colored brown.
It's not as warm and it's just dark
enough for my complexion. Like it
[clears throat] doesn't even really I
don't know if I even like it that much
because like low key, I do like to have
some contrast on my face. But I am
excited because I know I'm going to love
this. This is the Hourglass color that
we picked up yesterday in that lur
color.
Yeah, that's giving like black forest.
Oh yeah, spit on me. That is lovely.
Okay, actually I am going to add a bit
of the Kofi. I just like a little
browner.
That's better. Okay. And then this is
how you see like that glow that that sun
that spritz gives. Like that's what I
want. I know some people like the matte
look. Time and place, you know. I like
looking like the sun.
Put a little mole on the lip, you know,
so people know I'm feisty. And that's
the makeup. Welcome back to my channel.
Welcome back to my channel. Oh my god, I
haven't done an intro in so long.
Welcome back to the channel. Um, if
you're new here, hi. My name is Tia
Joelle. On this page, you know, we
really focus on trying to be the most
authentic you, okay? Not only the most
authentic you, but I want you to be the
best version of that authentic version
of you. I know I said a lot of versions
in that and I don't care. If you haven't
already, please make sure to like and
subscribe. And if you really like me, I
post every day and multiple times a day
across my short form platforms. I give
the people what they want. I do. I'm
reliable. I'm good old trusty dusty as
one will call. The chances of me
disappearing from the internet low. You
know, my digital footprint is already
immense. And um I'm like a cockroach.
You can't squish me. Well, you can, but
I'll be too quick and then I'll freak
you out and you run away.
It pains me to report, guys. Samuel L.
Jackson did not sleep with mommy last
night. What's your problem? probably
because I was cleaning till 1:00 a.m.
Answered my own damn question. I love
you, baby. I'm actually, even though I
didn't get that much sleep, like my
energy, I'm really excited to film today
because Let me show you. Let me show
you. I have a new gym outfit. I got new
gym clothes in the mail from Miss Honor
Active herself.
So, of course, we're going to try it on.
I think I have like four pieces in here.
Make it rain, baby. You know, I said
that one time at a daycare. I was just
joking, though. Okay, so listen. I know
everyone talks about the straight legs.
I get it. We love the straight legs, and
I have a lot of straight legs, but can
we get into the mother flares? Can we
get into that? Is that something we can
do? I like the flares personally more
than the straight legs. Something about
them, I think it just adds a little bit
more shape to my thigh and it just makes
me look a little shapier. Unless you
have the most ginormous in the world,
the straight leg, it's going to soften
what you already don't really have, you
know? And you know, my butt, she's
getting there. Plump, but she's not
there. She's not there. So, soft motion
flared bottoms in the color dusty
purple. Now, I am wearing a size medium
long. I can wear a size small. I've
never tried an extra small. I just feel
like that would be overkill, but I'm
wearing a size medium long. And one of
the reasons for that is ex when I used
to wear a lot of Honoractive, I used to
get a small and the smalls fit. Like
they suck me in. But like now I'm just
like, do I want to be feeling like I'm
baking a cake down there, you know? Like
I just want to be free. I want to be
free. So we will try this on. And then I
got a matching top. Respectfully, I'm
not the hugest fan of I don't mind it.
So these are the four soft fitted off
the shoulder top. And then I got it in
dusty purple and I have this in a size
extra small. I do recommend sizing down
on these tops because they uh you can
size down on them. They're you see that
you know and I like to be able to say
they're called for soft. They are soft
as they are soft as foruck. Sorry, I
don't know what I'm trying to say. We'll
try this on. I'm going to do like a
little mini fashion show.
[music]
So yeah, that's top number one. I don't
think this color looks that great on my
skin to be honest. But super cute. Nips
galore. Go ahead and ignore that. But
they have like this cute little
spy thing in them. And then the pants
are really long and I love that. That
really gets me going. Drag a little bit
on the floor. That is super cute. I'm
out of breath. Okay, this next color we
have. This is the color I'm going to
wear today. I can already feel it.
[laughter] You spicy spicy naughty girl.
Soft Motion minimal halterneck bralette
in rose pink. That doesn't make any
sense. It's got the wrong tag on this,
but whatever. This is the flared
leggings in rose pink. Now, I actually
got these ones in a small. Oh, no. I
didn't get these in a small. That's the
wrong lettering. This is also medium on.
And then I got the bralette top to match
it. I like a matching top. I I like not
matching, but also like I like looking
like I go to a private school. That is a
stunning color. That's going to My
skin's about to go crazy.
You're going to blow your when you see
this one. Oh wow. Wow. Wow. Look at this
color on my skin. Let me say something
real quick about pinks. Pinks. I'm very
particular about pink. And by that I
mean I'm not particular at all. I love
them all typically. But this pink in
particular, it's coming on camera like
it's really bright. And I would be lying
if I said it wasn't really bright in
real life as well. However, it is a
bluetoned pink. I have never in my life
owned a pair of activew wear that is a
blue tone pink. Like for instance, like
when you think about like this is like
black girl pink. Do you know what I mean
when I say that? Like this is black girl
pink. Think about getting a blush that
looks ashy on your face and they're just
not being enough blue in it. Okay. To
like really bring out the color. That's
this. Let's take a moment for the bra.
I'm not moisturized yet, so don't say
anything. They're regular waisted.
They're regular waisted. I just wear
them low-waisted cuz I can. You know,
that's the beautiful thing about Free
Well. I can do whatever I want. I don't
know. What do you guys think? Should I
wax? It's like not that bad, dude. My
[clears throat]
This is going to be a really TMI girl
moment, okay? So, if you're not here for
that, I need you to scroll up 30
seconds. I cannot be the only person
this happens to. I support bush life. I
love having a bush down there. Don't
mind. I think it's very womanly. I think
it's regrown. Okay. One of the few
negatives about being a supporter of
bush life and living that life is when
your hair follicle pokes right through
the fabric. So, I'm literally looking at
one of my pubes right now poking right
through the fabric. He's strong. That
one. Yeah. This is cute. This is cute.
Oh my god. So, let me ask you guys this.
Okay. And I'm asking, do I vlog weird?
Is this a weird way to vlog? Because I
had someone they in my comments new
stink. And if you're watching the stink,
I love you, Stink. She was like, "Oh, I
love the way that you vlog. It's so
different. Like, it's refreshing." I
didn't realize I was vlogging
differently. You know, I'm a consumer of
content. And I know every everyone has a
lot of stuff to say, but also guys like
setting your camera up and having the
aesthetic like let me walk through my
house and like let me change the camera
every 17 angles for me just to speak to
the camera. Like there are some people
who are going to do that and there are
some people who aren't. And
unfortunately if you guys want these
longer ass vlogs, I'm going to be
someone that doesn't, you know. So I'm
sorry that sometimes it's not that
aesthetic. But I'm tired. I don't think,
you know, for my people who have
attempted to do YouTube and are actively
doing YouTube, you know, like this is no
easy feat. YouTube alone is a full-time
job. And that's not even to mention like
you also being consistent on short form
platforms and finding relevancy. So, you
kind of just have to sacrifice things
when you do. Like, not everything is
going to be perfect and it's not going
to look amazing all the time. And like
you kind of just like have to be okay
with that. Like even if you get like an
editor, like the editor is not going to
edit like you and you sometimes just got
to be okay with with whatever comes out.
Okay. I saw this one girl. Let me show
you. She took the for top. She took the
form top. I'm actually just going to
slide this up. I don't Does anyone else
like sometimes just like not ever feel
like putting things over their head?
Like any opportunity I have to slide it
up from underneath, I'll take it because
like I just can't be
and she just like tied it. This looks
stupid. Let me adjust it. Give me a
second. Trust the process. Like it's
like a little cover up. Like I obviously
this is not how you're supposed to wear
it, but like is this not cute? Like am I
tripping right now? What if I was like
ooh look I'm sporty. I'm sporty. I'm
sporty. And then like the whole back is
exposed. Do we like it? Like is it cute?
You guys don't like it? It doesn't
matter. If I regret this later on, I
regret it later on. THIS IS CUTE.
[screaming]
I just love living alone. That's what
this is. Oh, you know what? I want to
use a new scent. I've been using the
same perfume for a minute. Let's switch
it up. I'm feeling really girly. So,
Jose Margan Oil Body Butter. That is my
go-to. You guys know that. I'm [snorts]
actually just wanted to say that I
really love you guys. Like I'm like
really grateful for life and I really
love you guys and like I'm so happy that
I feel so comfortable to share all these
sides of me cuz I know it's like a lot.
I know it's a lot. I know it's a lot. I
know it's a lot. But I don't know. I
just feel like we have really good
relationship. Maybe you don't. Maybe you
don't. Maybe you don't. Maybe it's I'm
just random. I don't know what I'm
saying. You guys, what I will say though
about the Joe's Moran, as much as I love
it, I'm not really sure how much that
scent be sticking. And if anyone else
has tried this and like thinks the same
thing, like can we talk about it in the
comments cuz I like need to know. Like
is it me or maybe I'm just like so nose
blind to it at this point that like I
can't hear it. And then the perfume. I'm
using the Kylie Jenner perfume in
cosmic. This is like actually a really
lovely perfume. I just have a lot of
perfumes now. So I was just like oh I
want to pick a signature scent and stick
with it. But like I don't have to do
that. I can switch my scent up every day
if I want to. And just like clothes I
was talking to you guys all like you
know finding your personal style and
like yes finding your personal style is
important. Yes, making sure that like
you wake up and you know you try to get
dressed every day. You never know who
you're going to meet. You never know.
Like, you know, everyone's always going
to have an impression of you and I want
my impression to be mysterious, bad,
sexy, fun, and amazing, you know? But
like, I think at that point I was so
bent on, okay, like I really want all of
my wardrobe to feel the same way. But
then I was just like, I don't have to do
that. Like, if I want to wear a crappy
t-shirt with some oversized jeans and
some flip-flops and that be like the
oversized like cutesy look, I can do
that. And if I want to look like a
40-year-old milk, I can do that. Like
that's the whole beautiful part about
being a human being is that you get to
choose which character you want to play,
you know? And it doesn't have to be the
same thing every day. I just feel so
free. What is going on with me right now
to ruin this entire outfit, guys? I'm
going to put a bandana with it. Now, I
saw Chrissy Chella. I saw her do this.
She was wearing Well, to be fair, I've
been I've been wearing bandanas. Like,
that's I've been wearing that's not a
I'm not copying her on that. But what I
will say is I saw her wear a blue
bandana with this outfit and I was like
m okay blue tone pink blue bandana like
is it just getting dumb now? Like should
I just like not do this? Hold up with
the bandana. I took the top off cuz I
felt like the top was like too like
girly feminine for me to like wear the
cool HIKER GIRL BANDANA. YEAH, I mean I
like it. What do you guys think? Also, I
did just let me show you this. So I
finally like caved and I got one of
those Dove those did I say dove? Forgot
what this is called. Lush body oil bars.
That's this. Round of applause for her.
That's what we'll say. Put on
deodorants. Already sitting my ass. I
don't really know what else I can do.
Okay, I'm hungry. Time to have a little
pre-workout snack.
Okay, let's talk about pre-workout
snack. Also, do you guys like my bowl? I
painted that. I didn't make the bowl,
obviously. Like, it's really expensive
actually to go and make pottery. Didn't
know that. But I did paint it. She's
very, very cute. She is a wash by hand
type of bowl though. I did realize that
with my other stuff. Anyway, pre-workout
snack. You guys know what the vibe is.
I'm having musli. It is a delicious
blend of whole grain cereal, dried
fruit, and nuts. No added sugar. And I
really like the ingredients. Let's look
at these ingredients here. Eight flakes,
toasted wheat flakes, raisins, flacked
almonds, and hazelnuts. I know what all
of those ingredients are. So, I'm
actually at the end of this. I bought
another one already, but I'm going to go
ahead and finish this off. Especially on
my leg days, I like to have That doesn't
look like a lot. It is a lot. You can
like warm this up, too. I guess this is
like I'm just eating oatmeal cold.
Really? That's kind of what's happening
here. Now, I [applause] have lactade,
but I also have the Fair Life Lactoseree
milk in there. That one has a little bit
more protein, but I'm not wasteful, so
I'm going to finish this. Yeah, that's
about good. I'm not measuring any of
this [\h__\h] Going to put a bit of honey
in there. I'm not measuring. Why am I
not measuring? I'm not measuring.
Because I have been tracking food and
doing this for so long, I have a really
good idea about what the portions look
like. Okay, I'm about to do a tablespoon
of honey, which is actually more than
you think. I'm going to do a bit of
salt, you know, to really get them
electrolytes in. Why? Because I want to
be speedy and quick. High key though,
like I don't know if it's me cuz I'm in
America, but like every time I'm like in
Europe, I'm like, "Oh, this meal needs
some goddamn salt." And like I'm hoping
that's not the American in me. Like I'm
hoping that's not the insufferable part
of America. Like where we just kind of
can't like live without salt in our
food. And what if it is? And then so I'm
going to eat this little cereal mix and
then I'm going to have two boiled eggs.
Boiled eggs part is just because I know
that after I work out in the gym, I'm
not going to want to eat this. I have
like a really bad boiled egg and I think
I'm going to start cooking them on the
pan soon cuz I'm getting about sick
tired of them mother things. And so
yeah, that's my breakfast. Well, it's
not my breakfast. That's my pre-workout
snack slash a portion of my breakfast is
with it with the eggs. So, here's the
thing, right? If you want to sustain
muscle, you have to eat. There's no way
around that. Okay? So, and and this is
the thing, right? Like this is even like
when it comes to like GLPs or peptides
or anything like that. When someone gets
on that drug and they haven't like
previously been in the gym or they don't
previously already have like muscle
mass, they tend to look really flat and
deflated. That's also not the goal. It's
important to get the weight off, right?
Because there is just a lot of there's a
huge correlation with atapost tissue
[music] in your health. Higher that is,
the more at risk you are for a lot of
things. But the other part of that is
that it's also really important to make
sure that you have muscle, right?
Especially as a woman. We're not talking
about men. Especially as a woman, okay?
It's really important you have that. And
in order to have that and sustain it and
keep it, maintain it, you have to feed
it. There's always going to be points in
times, like even like on my page of
people will sit there and be like, "Oh,
like you're not eating. You're not
eating." Baby, you don't have to worry
about that cuz Big Papa loves a meal.
Like I love food. I love everything
about food. And like I just was thinking
I'm like, damn. Like I can't imagine
living in a world and not being able to
look at my phone on TikTok at all the
New York restaurants, writing down and
saving what I'm going to eat when I'm
out there. Like I I love food and I
think it's important to enjoy it. But
again, like you're going to have to
enjoy it with balance. Okay. So, a
majority of my life, 90% of my life
looks very balanced and and very healthy
and very on it. And then there's that
percent like where maybe I'll go get a
little ice cream, you know, I have a
little ice cream date or like and I'll
have a nice meal, you know, or like I'll
go out and I'll have like a sweet treat
because I want to, but I can do that
because 90% of my life looks like this.
You know, when you're busy, it's not
hard to stay on track with your goals,
right? Like when you have time to think
about food is when it makes it a little
bit harder. But when you have meals that
you enjoy and that you like and they get
the job done and they make you feel
satisfied, not only do you save money
from not going out as much, um, but you
don't feel as guilty when you do choose
to go out. You know, there's give and
take with everything. Talked about this
before, but in terms of supplements,
again, I'm only taking creatine as like
my main like sports supplement thing. A
lot of you guys have asked me in the
past, and by past I mean present. Oh,
like you know what? If I'm on a weight
loss journey, like should I take
creatine? First off, you're on a fat
loss journey. You don't want to lose
weight, right? You want to lose fat. We
want to keep our muscle. We want to keep
our shape, right? You want to lose fat.
Second off, yes, if you're on a weight
loss journey, if you're on a fat loss
journey, if you're on a muscle gain
journey, if you're on a weight gain
journey, you should absolutely take
creatine. This is by no means a
superpower drug. Like, this is not going
to change your life by no means, but
this is going to help progress the rate
of your journey, okay? Not by a crazy
amount. You know, you're not taking
steroids, but it's an amazing
supplement. I've talked about it before.
I can link some of my old videos that I
have mentioned and referenced in depth
if you guys want in my description box
down below. Now, other than that, I'm
taking a fiber supplement just to make
sure everything's moving along in there.
And if I feel like I'm having a hard
time with my gut, I'll take a digestive
enzyme with my food. But yeah, like
that's about it, you know? Cute, simple,
calm, collected. Yeah, like it's just
like cold mush.
But I like it. I'm telling you, you guys
got to stay away from the processed
food. Like that's what's making this
journey harder. All right, I'm going to
finish this and let's go gym.
Hallelujah.
I've done a thing. [laughter]
How do we feel about them? [snorts]
[gasps] You know, I'm feeling like I
need a bit of validation with it because
Yeah. Like, is it cool? Like is it just
being like, "Wow, like that girl's so
cool. I never get red. Maybe I'll get
red." Is it giving that? Like is it
giving hm never thought to get that?
Maybe I will. Or is it giving grandma
fingers? You know, like which one is it
doing? Is it sexy, grown, and fine? Or
is it old, mature, and age? Not that
there's anything wrong with being old,
mature, or aged either. Okay. I love my
grandma. Love both my grandmas. But I
don't know. Like I'm trying I I'm going
to keep looking in the viewfinder, so
like please ignore me. But like I'm
trying to like do I like it? I don't
know. Yeah, I would have took you guys
with me in there. Like the workout I had
to like literally this is how I know I
be bullshitting the gym because I did
that workout. I couldn't get the steps
in or and I'm not going to get the steps
in today just because like my sleep was
so bad. And so I'm just going to try and
like get [music] some like rest in and
like not push it too hard, but I did my
full workout good intensity from start
to finish. It took me 29 minutes and
that's with 2 to 3 minute rest between
each of the exercises. I was like,
"Okay, like clearly I am bullshitting
because usually that workout would take
me double the time. 50 minutes or so, I
would say, but that took me I' I've
somehow cut out 20 minutes and I'm not
sure at what point that was. Maybe I'm
not talking or maybe I just look like I
needed to hustle." I also see people in
the comments like under not my videos,
but people being like, "Guys, like don't
listen to, you know, to the influencers
like not all of us have 2 3 4 hours to
spend in the gym." Baby girl, I'd be in
and out of that mother. If I'm in the
gym longer than an hour and a half, the
way that that ruins my entire day, like
I don't like being in the gym long. I
like getting the work done. I like
getting my steps in and calling it a
goddamn day. I can't speak for other
influencers, but I sure as hell can
speak for myself that I am not in there
longer than an hour and a half. Even my
workouts, like I don't even have enough
sets in my workouts to be in there an
hour and a half. But also, can we talk
about how like my glute look a little
plump in that? We don't have talk. We're
talking about it in like a fitness way,
not in a sexual way. So, if you're going
to say something gross in the comments,
get out of here cuz I don't like that.
My glutes, like especially like since
being home, since the last video that I
posted, they're finally starting to look
up in life and I'm just proud of them.
Also, today is the day that I announced
that I'm an Honoractive athlete. If it
wasn't already clear by all the hints
that I dropped, yes, I'm their newest
move ambassador. The video that I posted
was incredibly amazing, fun, like just
an add a drop of just like humor to it.
And I think it's a representation of my
page. And I'm I'm grateful to be a part
of a team like this. This is the new
drop what I was wearing, which I think I
already talked about earlier. Code
stink. Okay. Code stink. Sorry, I didn't
mean to yell at you. But yeah, hopefully
this stuff is still in stock by Sunday.
But if it's not, like I just got the
package yesterday, so it kind of is what
it is, which is why you should be
following my show from platforms because
I do talk about the things more often.
Not that I'm fishing [music] for a
follow, but also like, you know, like do
you want more of me or not? This could
just be enough. This is a lot. So I get
that. No hard feelings. My favorite line
from Honoractive is soft motion. I used
to be someone that loved the effortless
seamless. I am not an effortless
seamless girl anymore. I'm a soft
motion. I am a comfort over and honestly
is effortless or the enhanced lift like
are those more practical for the gym?
Like yeah, like maybe. And it makes your
butt look incredible and amazing, but
like baby girl, I'm in my comfort era.
Okay. I had someone be like, "Oh yeah,
like you know, we know that you lift
like crazy and blah blah and do all
this." No, I I don't lift like I I lift
like a normal human being in the gym,
you know? So, when someone said that to
me, I was like, "Hey, like that's not
the type of I'm a cutesy, fun, healthy
living lifestyle girl. I'm not like a,
you know, I'm not like that in the gym.
Like, that's not what I do. I'm just
trying to enjoy life." Yeah. So, I love
soft motion. I get the flares more than
I get the straight legs. I know
everybody loves straight legs, but like
I have both straight legs and the
flares. And I'm telling you right now,
like the flares just fit me delectable.
Like it's just sexy, cute, young. Like
it gives young hoe. [music] You know,
flares give like if you got a big butt,
it gives young hoe. But if you don't
have like the biggest butt in the world,
it just gives Okay. Like I like it. This
is nice. But the flares give this is
hot. And like I just want to be hot
forever. Yeah. And what I'm going to do
in the future, especially when I'm
talking about interactive cuz obviously
like the drops are going to come. If I
don't get the clothes before they drop,
I know stuff sells out. I'm only going
to try and push to you guys clothes that
are in stock. So if it's not in stock,
like I'm not about to sit here and tell
you like, "Oh, like you can get like
this is what I'm wearing. Get this." And
like by the time you guys get to it,
it's out of stock. Cuz that's not what
we're doing. A lot of the Soft Motion,
which is what I'm wearing, is in stock
and they do do frequent restocks because
the way that like I be looking at that
website just like y'all. Come on now. Do
you guys like the nails? I'm sorry. I
just feel like I should bring it back to
that. Are we kind of with what's
happening here? I get mixed reviews all
the time. Everyone's going to have their
own opinion. Someone put a comment and
one time and they were just like, "Yeah,
girl. Like love like the Bob makes you
look older." I'm like, "Yeah, like
that's not necessarily a bad thing. Do
the nails make me look older though? If
they do make me look older, is that a
hit against me or is it just like this
is mature, right? Can we debate this in
the comments? Real opinions only. So,
yeah, we're going to go inside. I'm not
going to film too much more for you guys
like in terms of like I I I've been
doing a lot of chats. Like, I've been
doing a lot of yapping and like that's
how I ended up getting to that hour
video last week. I like I'm telling you,
I did not realize that was going to be
[music] an hour, but I think I'm just
getting more comfortable with talking to
you guys on the camera. I'm using my
imagination. There are a couple of home
projects that I want to do. My paper
lamp is boring. my paper limb. She's
boring. She's white. I want to make her
tan, you know? So, I saw this little DIY
trick. I bought some stuff like that.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to
get to it today, but if I can't, we'll
do it tomorrow. And yeah, like I really
just want to work on like slowly but
surely making my house more of me and
less of just blank canvases wall. I
think I've done a really really good job
with like my living room and my dining
room area. But I still want to like
maybe do some paper, some I'm saying
some paper, [music] some some contact
paper or like some fake tiles like
renter friendly style cuz I don't want
to have a hard time peeling it off. So
that means I got to get like cardboard
on top of it. Whatever. We'll figure it
out. That's really what I want to do for
[music] the next couple of months. I
always get into this headsp space where
like I'll start a project and then like
I'll stop doing the project. I don't
want that to keep being my reality. So
yeah, [music] that's what the rest of
this video is going to be. Less yap.
Unless you guys like the app. Do you
like the app or is it too much? Guys,
checking in. I don't like my nails. I
don't like my nails, you know? Like you
guys, some of you guys gave me
validation cuz I post this on my TikTok,
but unfortunately like I just like can't
convince myself to like this. They're
not bad. There's nothing wrong with
them, but I don't know. Like I kind of
got little granny fingers. So, I already
like rebooked a nail appointment for
Wednesday. They got me. Okay. Like, but
like listen, you have to try something
new to know you don't like it, you know?
And I'm willing to try anything once
except for like heroin or like meth. I
feel like I can live life without
knowing what those feel like. But the
other things, yeah, like I'd be I'd be
down [music] once.